[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "65a8e127963d998e4220c04d"
  },
  "level_name": "Level_3",
  "sublevels": [
    {
      "question": "What does 'mon mari' mean?",
      "options": [
        "My sister",
        "My husband",
        "My son",
        "My father"
      ],
      "correct_option": "My husband"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say 'my wife' in French?",
      "options": [
        "ma fille",
        "ma femme",
        "ma sœur",
        "ma mère"
      ],
      "correct_option": "ma femme"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate 'mes parents' to English.",
      "options": [
        "My grandparents",
        "My parents",
        "My children",
        "My nephew"
      ],
      "correct_option": "My parents"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English translation of 'mon frère'?",
      "options": [
        "My brother",
        "My grandfather",
        "My niece",
        "My cousin"
      ],
      "correct_option": "My brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "If 'ma tante' is mentioned, who is being referred to?",
      "options": [
        "My sister",
        "My aunt",
        "My mother",
        "My daughter"
      ],
      "correct_option": "My aunt"
    }
  ]
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "65a8e1be963d998e4220c04f"
  },
  "level_name": "Level_2",
  "sublevels": [
    {
      "question": "Which is number 5?",
      "options": [
        "un",
        "sept",
        "deux",
        "huit"
      ],
      "correct_option": "un"
    },
    {
      "question": "There are __ wonders of the world",
      "options": [
        "cinq",
        "sept",
        "trois",
        "huit"
      ],
      "correct_option": "sept"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the first day of the week?",
      "options": [
        "lundi",
        "samedi",
        "jeudi",
        "mardi"
      ],
      "correct_option": "lundi"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which one is Wednesday?",
      "options": [
        "vendredi",
        "samedi",
        "jeudi",
        "mercredi"
      ],
      "correct_option": "mercredi"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is May?",
      "options": [
        "janvier",
        "mars",
        "peut",
        "septembre"
      ],
      "correct_option": "peut"
    },
    {
      "question": "Christmas is celebrated in ______?",
      "options": [
        "decembre",
        "septembre",
        "peut",
        "fevrier"
      ],
      "correct_option": "decembre"
    },
    {
      "question": "Today is ____ fool's day",
      "options": [
        "julliet",
        "avril",
        "peut",
        "septembre"
      ],
      "correct_option": "avril"
    }
  ]
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "65a8e2d1963d998e4220c053"
  },
  "level_name": "Level_1",
  "sublevels": [
    {
      "question": "What does 'Bonjour' mean?",
      "options": [
        "Good evening",
        "Goodbye",
        "Good day",
        "Hi"
      ],
      "correct_option": "Good day"
    },
    {
      "question": "How would you say 'See you later' in French?",
      "options": [
        "Bonne nuit",
        "À bientôt",
        "Salut",
        "Au revoir"
      ],
      "correct_option": "À bientôt"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English translation of 'Voici . . . /Voilà . . .'?",
      "options": [
        "There is . . . /Here is . . .",
        "Let me introduce . . . to you",
        "Have a good day",
        "What’s . . . name?"
      ],
      "correct_option": "There is . . . /Here is . . ."
    },
    {
      "question": "When someone says 'Salut,' how would you respond?",
      "options": [
        "See you soon",
        "Goodbye",
        "Hi",
        "Have a good day"
      ],
      "correct_option": "Hi"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate 'Je m’appelle . . .' to English.",
      "options": [
        "What’s . . . name?",
        "My name is . . .",
        "Let me introduce . . . to you",
        "To call"
      ],
      "correct_option": "My name is . . ."
    }
  ]
}]